Preliminary Inventory to the Lieutenant Bielevskii collection 1917
Hoover Institution Archives
Lieutenant Bielevskii collection,
1917
XX039
Bielevskii, Lieutenant, collector.
1 folder (0.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Military reports and memoranda, relating to the abdication of Tsar Nicholas II, and to disintegration of discipline in the Russian Army during the Russian Revolution.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
Nicholas II, Emperor of Russia, 1868-1918; Russia; Russia--History--February Revolution, 1917; Russia. Armiia
Container List
- Manifest Gosudaria Imperatora (Box 1.)
- Russia. Armiia, 12 Armiia: Prikaz #621 18 iunia, 1917
- Russia. Armiia, 12 Armiia: Ustav organizatsii ofitserov i chinovnikov shtaba 20 i 21 april 1917
- Russia. Armiia, 6 Sibirskogo Korpusa: Vypiska iz Donesenii Komkora 6 Sibirskogo Korpusa, ot 6-ogo sentiabria za #06595
- Russia. Armiia, 2 Sibirskogo Korpusa: Raport #04040, 26 okt. Deistvuiushchaia armiia
- Russia. Armiia, 12 Armiia: Zamietki o distsipline v Russkoi Armii, #1295, 4 april 1917
- Svodka svedenii o nastroenii armii s 20 sentiabria posle oktiabria 1917
- Ditto: 1 po 15 oktiabria 1917
- Obiasnitel'naia zapiska k tablitse svedenii o sostoianii armii za vremia s 15 po 30 oktiabria 1917
- Kopiia pisma poluchennogo v oktiabrie 1917g. v stavke na imia Verkhovnogo Glavnocomanduiushchego Kerenskogo